CURRICULUM VITAE

CONTACT DETAILS

Name	Oliver Tomondy
Birth date	March 2000
Nationality	Slovak
Address	Na Kope X/26, 040 01 Košice, Slovakia
Phone	+421 949 544 711
Email	oliver.tomondy@gmail.com



OBJECTIVE STATEMENT

As a Front End Developer with 4 years experience, I am looking for opportunities to work on challenging projects and am prepared to contribute to the success of your company with my knowledge and skills. I am responsible, open-minded and eager to gain experience and learn new technologies.

EDUCATION

Sep 2014 - Present	 Bilingual German-Slovak Grammar school, Opatovská cesta Mathematics, ITComputing, German, English, Excellent grades in each subject
Sep 2016 - Jun 2017	 Sperlgymnasium, Wien, Austria Exchange student IT & Computing, French,

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Aug 2017 - Present (1 year, 8 months)	 Front End Developer - OneClick.Systems - part-time We create websites and e-shops for customers in our advanced all-in-one CMS that we develop My job is to develop front end capabilities of the CMS (templates, plugins, modules management etc)
2015 - Present	 Working on various private projects Runfan - Fitness tracker - web app SimplyNote - Note-taking web app Change Yourself - Website for a civic association

ABILITIES

Languages	English - Full working proficiency German - Full working proficiency (C1 Certificate) Czech - Full working proficiency Italian - Limited working proficiency French - Elementary proficiency Slovak - Native
IT Skills	HTML, CSS3, SASS, LESS JavaScript, JQuery, VueJS, AJAX, PHP, MySQL, JSON Bootstrap, Materialize, GIMP Git, SVN, Jira Knowledge of UI/UX principles, responsive design
Characteristics	communicative, reliable, responsible, analytical skills and a strong will to learn, punctual, flexible, adaptable, stress-tolerant

CERTIFICATIONS AND AWARDS

Deutsches Sprachdiplom (C1) - DSD II (2019)

2nd place on national WEB competition Junior Internet with Runfan (2018)

Erasmus+ Youthpass certificate - Design Thinking training course (2018)

HOBBIES

I am an active swimmer and a fitness enthusiast. I enjoy learning foreign languages, reading books, meeting new people from around the world on several Erasmus+ projects and, unsurprisingly, doing various IT stuff. Besides that, I am a passionate traveller and nature lover.